evenue.net 2014-12-08

# Privacy Policy « Paciolan

Visitors to our site can submit comments or questions about our products and services and request information or to be added to our mailing list. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at this site include: name, organization name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and information about your interest in and use of our products and services.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

We use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products and services, and to respond to your inquiries about our offerings. We also use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you about updates to products and services, or to assist you with any questions you have about an order you have placed for products and services.

From time to time, we may use the personally identifiable information that we collect to offer you other products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

We may use “cookies” to enhance your experience with our site. Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to customize your experience at our Web page. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you have any questions about the privacy policy for this site, you may contact us at: [legal@paciolan.com](mailto:legal@Paciolan.com)

### Electronic Communications

When you visit this Site or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on this Site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

### Miscellaneous

These Terms contain the entire understanding and supersede all prior understandings of the parties hereto relating to the subject matter hereof, and cannot be changed or terminated orally. If there is a determination that any provision of these Terms is invalid or unenforceable under applicable law, that determination will not affect the rest of these Terms, and these Terms shall be deemed amended to the minimum extent necessary to make them valid and enforceable. The failure of Paciolan to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. Regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action against Paciolan arising out of or related to use of this Site or under these Terms must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. The section titles in these Terms are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.
